Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Safety and Security Department, 1988-present UPG.RG.28
ULS Greensburg
University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Safety and Security Department
1988-present
ULS Greensburg
University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
UPG.RG.28
1 box
Administrative Records of the Safety and Security Department of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, 1988-present.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Custodial History
Transferred from the Safety and Security Department to the UPG Archives.
Scope and Content Notes
Brochures, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Forms, Memoranda, Police Blotter, Publications, News Clippings
Universities and colleges –- Pennsylvania –- Greensburg –- Records and correspondence; Universities and colleges -– Pennsylvania -– Greensburg -– Administration; University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
- Brochures, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Forms, 1988-2019; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  For Safety's Sake 1994-95. [1995] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 1995-96 [1996] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 1996-97. [1996] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 1997-98. [1997] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 1998-99. [1998] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 1999-2000. [1999] 8 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2000-2001. [2000] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2001-2002. [2001] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2002-2003. [2002] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2003-2004. [2003] [22 p.] [This copy printed from e-mail.]
  For Safety's Sake 2004-2005. [2004] [22 p.] [This copy printed from e-mail.]
  For Safety's Sake 2005-2006. [2005] [22 p.] [This copy printed from e-mail.]
  For Safety's Sake 2006-2007. [2006] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2007-2008. [2007] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2008-2009. [2008] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2009-2010. [2009] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2010-2011. [2010] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake 2011-2012. [2011] 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2012. 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2013. 12 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2014. 16 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2015. 29 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2016. 29 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2017. 29 p.
  For Safety's Sake. Fall 2019. 34 p. [This copy downloaded from web site: greensburg.pitt.edu/safety.]
  Leaflet. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Office of Safety and Security. November Tip Sheet. Campus Safety Tips. Identity Theft. [2005]
  Leaflet. Parking at UPG. Department of Safety and Security. [2006]
  Leaflet. Student Parking at UPG. Dept. of Safety and Security. [2000]
  [Mailer] Subject: "Pennsylvania College and University Security Information Act (PA Act 73)" University of Pittsburgh Greensburg [1988]
  [Form] Telephone Threat Checklist [undtd]
  [Form] University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Request for Wedding Photographs [undtd]
  [Form] University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Dept. of Safety and Security. Silent Witness Form [2000?]
  Parking Ordinance [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg] August 2019. [This Ordinance defines the general operation and policies of traffic and parking at the University of Pittsburgh--Greensburg Campus].[This print copy is downloaded from: https://www.greensburg.pitt.edu/sites/default/files/PARKORD%20UPG=Revised/20FY2019.pdf.]
  - Brochures, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Forms, 1988-2017 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- Memoranda, 2000-2018; II.
  2000, Aug. 27. From: Horan. To: [Faculty and Staff]. Subject: Jeanne Cleary Disclosure. [The Jeanne Cleary Disclosure of Campus Security Policy and Campus Crimes Statistics (formerly the Campus Security Act)
  2001, Apr. 5. [From: Thomas D. Horan. To: UPG Community. Subj.: Appointment] [announcement of the promotion of Simeon C. McClean, Sr. to post of Assistant Director of Safety and Security]
  2001, Oct. 11. TDH to all Department Heads. Subject: Van Policy in re "...all vans owned by the University of Pittsburgh..."
  2005, July 13 via e-mail. To: upgpolice@pitt.edu [cc To: UPG Faculty/Staff] Subject: New Members. [Announces the appointment of new members of the Dept. of Safety and Security: Robin Shuglie and Jared Stern.]
  2005, Sept. 2 via e-mail. From: Thomas D. Horan [To: UPG Faculty/Staff] Subject: Van Crash. [A 15 passenger van from the University of Utah State crashed on a highway 65 miles north of Salt Lake City. A driver and 7 students were killed when the van overturned. In 2001, UPG instituted a van certification program to educate and provide training when operating these vans.]
  2010, July 22. [Ltr. Format] [From: Sharon P. Smith, President. To: Dear Colleagues] [Subj.: Message from Pres. Smith in re Commander Schreiber.] [Announces the appointment, by Exec. Vice Chancellor Jerome Cochran, of Kathleen Schreiber of the Pgh. Campus Police Dept. as Regional Commander who will interact regularly with the heads of the regional campus police departments on regional issues in all system discussions of safety and security. She will continue to report directly to Chief Delaney on the Pgh. campus. Commander Schreiber's office is on the Pitt-Greensburg campus. Appointment effective 7/1/10.]
  2015, Sept. 9. From: Carl A. Rossman, Jr. to [Campus Community] Subject: [New Chief of Campus Police, Daniel P. Lynch.]
  2015, Oct. 12. From: Pitt-Greensburg Campus Police. To: [Campus Community] Subject: Crime Alert 10/12/15 4:34 p.m. Non-specific threat Cassell Hall.
  2015, Oct. 12. From: Pitt-Greensburg Campus Police. To: [Campus Community] Subject: Crime Alert Cancelled 10/12/15 7:50 p.m. Situation involving Cassell Hall resolved. No unresolved issues. Resume all normal activities.
  2015, Nov. 5. From: Pitt-Greensburg Campus Police. To: Campus Community. [Police phone number 724-836-9865: out-of-service and restitution of service for Verizon phone service subscribers.]
  2016, July 26. To: Campus Community. Subj.: State Police Helicopter Coming to Campus...July 21...[as part of Camp Cadet experience.]
  2016, Aug. 2. To: Campus Community. Subj.: Table Top Exercise, Aug. 3. [...static exercise [by Pitt-Greensburg Campus Police and other area emergency response agencies] should a large scale emergency ever occur...on campus...]
  2016, Aug. 3. To: Campus Community. Subj.: 2016 Cleary Act Notice. [...required notification to member of the Campus Community by the Federal Cleary Act of emergency drills to better prepare for an actual emergency and that the University is prepared to respond to an emergeny incident occurring on campus.]
  2017, Apr. 20. From: Chief D. Lynch. To: Campus Community. Subj.: Campus Crime Alert [investigation of a prowling incident...asking campus residents to be aware...suggest precautionary measures to be taken.]
  2018, Feb. 19. Fr.: Pitt-Greensburg Campus Police. To: Campus Community. Subj.: Guest and Visitor Parking Passes. [...inquiry about visitor/guest parking policy...]
  - Memoranda, 2000-2018 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- Police Blotter, 2008-present; III.
  [Note: As posted in the The [UPG] Insider]
  2008/2009 Aug. 24 - Nov. 26, 2008/Jan. 5-Mar. 28, 2009 2009/2010 Aug. 2009/Mar. 2010 2010/2011 Aug. 7 - Nov. 8, Dec. 16, 2010/Jan.-Mar. 2011 2011/2012 Feb. - Mar., 2012 2012, Apr.-2014, Aug. [Not in UPG Archives] 2014, Sept12-2015, Nov. 19 2016, Jan. 9-16, Jan. 26-Feb. 8, Feb. 18-Mar. 14, Mar. 22-Apr. 8 2016, Aug. 26-Sept. 10, Sept. 8-Oct. 2 [Sept. 8, 11, 22], Oct. 3-16 [Oct. 3], Oct. 17-Nov. 9 [Oct. 11, 27, Nov. 1, 4, 5], Nov. 9-28 [Nov. 9, 18], 2016 2017, Jan. 3-31 [Jan. 3, 5, 15], Jan. 27-Feb. 21 [Jan. 27-31, Feb. 9, 14, 15, 16], Feb. 16-Mar. 2 [Feb. 16, 20, 23], Mar. 2-23 [Mar. 16, 20]. 2017, Aug. 3, 29, Sept. 11, 14, 22, 24, Oct. 2, 6, 20, 21, Nov. 20, 30, Dec. 1, 10, 15 2018, Jan., 12, 18, Feb, 23, 24 2018, Aug. 26, 28, Sept. 4, 11, 15, 17, 18, 30. Oct. 2, 4, 5, 12, 20, 21, Dec. 3, 14 2019, Jan. 17, Feb. 1, 2, 4, 7, 13
  See Also
  Series: Brochures. For Safety's Sake
  - Police Blotter, 2008-present (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- Publications, 2006-2009; IV.
  University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Parking Ordinance. June 2006. 33 p.
  University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Parking Ordinance. July 2008. 35 p.
  University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Parking Ordinance. Sept. 2009. 35 p.
  - Publications, 2006-2009 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- News Clippings, V.
  - News Clippings (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 7, Box 1)